# **Hubert Wyszyński**

**Fullstack Developer** 

+48 733 430 552 hub.wyszynski@gmail.com My tech blog: www.notondutytoday.com



## **ABOUT**

I am a software developer with nearly **7 years of experience in the industry.** I have worked extensively as both a front-end and back-end developer, gaining a comprehensive understanding of the entire software development lifecycle. I am based in Warsaw.

#### **SKILLS**

Throughout my career, I have gained experience with a wide range of technologies, including:

React, Redux, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, styled-component, Jest, React Testing Library, Node.js, Express, SQL, MySQL, Golang, gRPC, web sockets, git, HTTP protocol.

#### Languages:

- English fluent
- Polish native

#### **ADDITIONAL**

In late 2023 I took part in **AI Devs 2** course. A 5-week practical course on combining generative AI tools with application logic and automation tools.

I did it because I want to be somewhat up to date with industry trends.

Also, recently I have started my tech blog

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Warsaw University of Technology**

Automation and Robotics | 2013 - 2018

I hereby give consent for my personal data to be processed for the purpose of conducting recruitment for the position for which I am applying and all future processes.

applying and all future processes. Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych w celu prowadzenia rekrutacji na aplikowane przeze mnie stanowisko.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Fullstack Developer**

#### Text (previously LiveChat) | June 2022 - present

- responsible for building affiliate program application
- integrating with multiple APIs across company products as well as external ones
- working closely with product owner and designer on planning new features
- · defining APIs, defining database structure
- solving partners day-to-day issues
- full software development lifecycle: development, code reviews, testing, deployment
- tech stack: React, Redux, TypeScript, styledcomponents, Jest, unit testing, Golang, gRPC, web sockets, MySQL, Domain Driven Design
- working remotely

## Fullstack Developer Brytlyt | April 2020 - May 2022

- developing a data visualization tool
- Node.js (Express) for BE and React with TypeScript,
   Mapbox, Plotly
- onboarding new team members
- taking part in recruitment processes
- providing code reviews
- remote job

## **Frontend Developer**

### MoveCloser | June 2019 - April 2020

As a frontend developer I was involved in development of a user interface using **Vue.js**, ensuring responsive design and optimal performance.

#### **Frontend Developer**

Ideamotive | July 2018 - May 2019

Software house. I was working on frontend layer of apps with **React.** 

## **Frontend Developer**

Avrio Interactive | June 2018 - July 2018

Worked on projects for Polish clients, focusing on enhancing my front-end development skills.